## **Front-end Developer**

## Nur Fikri Kiki (He/Him)

https://kikiding.space

kikiding.space@gmail.com

https://github.com/codingki

I currently live in Yogyakarta, Indonesia (+7 UTC). I'm 25 years old. I'm a Front-end developer. React and Typescript are my main tools for building apps. I can describe my self as a designer who trapped in the mind of a programmer, I love building modern and beautiful app.

#### **Education**

#### University, Courses, Certifications etc.

Purwadhika, Tangerang, Indonesia (2016-2017) Amikom University, Yogyakarta, Indonesia (2019-2023)

#### **Skills**

HTML, CSS, Javascript, Typescript, Tailwind, Chakra UI, React, React native, Next.js, Electron, Figma

## **Experience**

### Front-end Developer @ Strangelove Ventures

May 2022 - Present, Remote

[Next.js, React, Typescript] Work with clients and internal projects. Help design, advise and deliver a user interface & experience.

#### Front-end Developer @ Accelbyte

Apr 2021 - May 2022, Yogyakarta/Remote

[Electron, React, Typescript]

Work with both internal and client's engineering teams to help design, advise, and deliver a user interface for both internal and external use that is highly functional, responsive, and lightweight based on UX design and backend APIs.

## **Awards, Featured Project**

# Second Place BNCC Technoscape X Tiket.com Hackathon (BINUS)

12 Okt 2020

[React Native, Expo, Javascript]
Creating mobile apps: An online concert ticket sales platform that can be purchased seperately
<a href="https://github.com/codingki/TikTeng">https://github.com/codingki/TikTeng</a>

#### React Native Rapi UI

2021

[React Native, Expo, Typescript, Figma]
Rapi UI is a UI components library for react native <a href="https://rapi-ui.kikiding.space">https://rapi-ui.kikiding.space</a>

#### Kawalcovid19.id

2021

[React, Styled components, Typescript]
Contribute to design, code and connecting the APIs the

#### Graz

2022

[Typescript, React]
Graz is a collection of React hooks containing everything you need to start working with the Cosmos ecosystem.
https://graz.strange.love/